<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<about>
	<intro>	
		<title><![CDATA[Welcome To The Tenderloin!]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[TenderVoice is an interactive web application which uses sound narratives to highlight community services and resources in the Tenderloin. It is designed to increase awareness about the service organizations in the neighborhood, as well as to serve as an educational tool for computer literacy.]]></description>
	</intro>
	
	<full>	
		<title><![CDATA[About TenderVoice]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[TenderVoice is an interactive web application which uses sound narratives to highlight community services and resources in the Tenderloin. It is designed to increase awareness about the service organizations in the neighborhood, as well as to serve as an educational tool for computer literacy. <br><br>TenderVoice users can be personally engaged in learning about resources available in the Tenderloin by hearing personal interviews with service providers.  The application includes a full organizational database and interactive map of community resources, as well as a game which tests the knowledge of users about the community resources. <br><br>This website is being used by our community partner, the Tenderloin Tech Lab, as a teaching tool for introducing interactive web-based applications to new computer users. <br><br>The project was developed as part of the City Centered Festival, sponsored by the Gray Area Foundation for the Arts and KQED in San Francisco. Please also take time to explore our sister project, TenderNoise, which maps trends of noise data collected over time throughout the neighborhood. <br><br>Objectives  <br><br>The stated goals of TenderVoice are to: <br>- Increase awareness of resources and service providers <br>  in the Tenderloin <br>- Help develop basic computer skills for residents  <br>  related to web interfaces and interactive media <br>- Create a meaningful connection between residents, <br>  their community, and digital technology <br>- Document the stories of the Tenderloin through digital <br>  media in a positive light <br>- Provide a new medium for learning about the neighborhood.  <br><br>Team  <br><br>TenderVoice was created and led by Jake Levitas and Mayra Madriz, and has been supported greatly by Alex Lyon of the Tenderloin Tech Lab. Jim Hovell designed and developed the web application in Flash and has transformed our initial ideas into reality. All interviews and audio editing have also been completed firsthand by the team, with over 7 hours of raw footage collected from 15 organizations thus far. <br> <br>Partners  <br><br>The Tenderloin Tech Lab is the Tenderloinís only technology center specializing in adult computer and employment skills training, which aids residents in overcoming the barriers to employment and accessing technology. Many of the design and strategic decisions for TenderVoice were geared directly toward the Tech Lab's service populations. The website will now serve as the home page for Tech Lab computers, being accessed by hundreds of Tenderloin residents every week. <br> <br>The San Francisco Study Center has been an instrumental community service provider since 1972, now focusing onorganizational development and publishing - including the local Tenderloin newspaper, the Central City Extra. In 2009, they published the HELP Resource Guide, a comprehensive guide to neighborhood resources in the Tenderloin and South of Market neighborhoods. TenderVoice has drawn upon HELP for inspiration and information about the plethora of community organizations in the area.]]></description>
	</full>
	
	<contact>	
		<title><![CDATA[Contact or Contribute]]></title>
		<description><![CDATA[We would love to hear from you. Questions, thoughts, stories, comments, or ideas for collaboration are welcome. <br><br>If you are a community resource in the Tenderloin and would like to be a part of the project, please get in touch and we will schedule an in-person interview as soon as possible. <br><br>If you are interested in contributing time, resources, or donations to the project, please let us know. <br><br>tendervoice.sf [at] gmail [dot] com]]></description>
	</contact>
	
	<game instructions="resources/Tenderloin_Tech_Lab/Audio/0_MissionShort.mp3">	
		<instructions head="Welcome To The Tenderloin!"><![CDATA[How well do you know the Tenderloin? Guess the location of a particular organization by listening to a short audio clip from a longer interview.]]></instructions>
		<instructions head="Instructions"><![CDATA[1. Listen to the sample by clicking on the game chip once. <br>2. Grab chip by pressing and holding down the mouse. <br>3. While holding down, move chip over to empty marker on the map. <br>4. Let go of the mouse. <br>5. Repeat Step 2 through 4 until all locations are filled. <br>6. When all spaces are filled click "Check Answers" to see how you did. <br><br>Hints: If you need a little help click "Hint" to see the names and locations of the organizations you have to choose from. ]]></instructions>
	</game>
</about>