<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<about>
	<body header="About The VR">	
		<textnode divider="xxx" title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room Cooperative of San Francisco is incorporated under the Cooperative Corporation laws and regulations set forth by the State of California. Accordingly, the Vapor Room Cooperative conforms to ALL City and State laws and regulations governing Cooperatives as well as Medical Cannabis Dispensaries.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx" title="Mission Statement" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room Cooperative of San Francisco is a Medical Cannabis Dispensary committed to serving member- patient needs with the highest level of compassion and professionalism. We strive to provide the finest quality medicine in a safe, relaxed, and comfortable environment. We are committed to establishing a healthy and caring community by educating our members and the public about the benefits of therapeutic cannabis. The Vapor Room Cooperative advocates compassion, tolerance and understanding towards people from all walks of life. We also understand the intrinsic need for communication between doctors, patients and cannabis providers in order to effectively serve the diverse needs of our members.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx" title="Location" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room Cooperative is located on the ground floor of a beautiful Victorian house in the heart of Lower Haight, which is in the heart of San Francisco, which everyone knows is actually the heart of the United States. Our address is 607A Haight Street [at Steiner St.]. We are served by Muni lines 6, 7, 71 and 22 as well as the J, K, L and M lines which are located nearby at the Church St. and Duboce St. Station.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx" title="Facility & Lounge" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room Cooperative features a walk in dispensary that provides therapeutic cannabis as well as a cozy lounge that comfortably fits 14 members at a time. Our facility has recently been renovated to conform to the highest standards set forth by the Americans with Disabilities Act [ADA]. We boast a beautiful wheelchair ramp as well as a spacious, accessible restroom that will accommodate all wheelchairs and lowered display counters and transaction area. Knowing that we are a facility that caters to many members of the community that have compromised immune systems we provide our members with sanitized pipes, bongs and vaporizer mouthpieces.

The Vapor Room Cooperative [VRC] distinguishes itself from other dispensaries by emphasizing the use of non- carbonizing vaporizers as a healthy method of introducing THC into the body and is one of few dispensaries officially permitted to allow on- site consumption of therapeutic cannabis. There are multiple Volcano brand vaporizers distributed throughout the lounge for patients to use free of charge. These vaporizers are considered by many to be the best vaporizer available today although they remain cost prohibitive to many of our fixed income members. We have installed an efficient air filtration HVAC system with an outtake vent to remove all residual smoke and an intake vent to provide constant fresh air. Here you can feel free to relax with fellow members and share your experiences with others in the community. We also offer an array of non- smoking cannabis options, such as tinctures, salves as well as cannabis infused condiments and edibles. The VRC is highly committed to being an ecologically responsible member of this planet. We use biodegradable cups and utensils, we recycle and compost all appropriate waste and only use natural, non- toxic cleaners and products.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx" title="Community Alliance Program" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room Cooperative would like to thank all of our neighbors, member- patients and non- members alike, for their continued support throughout the years. We would also like to graciously thank all of our neighbors and community leaders who have maintained an open dialogue as well as an open mind, with us during the unique and arduous regulatory    process for Medical Cannabis Dispensaries in San Francisco.

In addition to being a positive influence in our member’s lives, we wish to be a positive influence in our local community. Over the years, the Vapor Room Cooperative has significantly developed its community outreach efforts.  One exciting component of the outreach is our rapidly evolving Community Alliance Program. This program’s purpose is to create and nurture relationships with neighborhood and citywide organizations and programs. By working with these organizations through volunteer services and donations we engage in implementing positive solutions to the Lower Haight’s many unique issues. In addition to making regular donations to Alliance members throughout the year, we collaborate with them on our general outreach efforts, promote their events, recruit volunteers and share resources.

All funds beyond the required amount for proper operation of the Vapor Room Cooperative are either donated to local charities or reinvested in providing a fuller experience for our members. We give generous donations on a regular basis to local youth and community groups including; after- school programs and summer camps for children, the San Francisco Police Department Officers Association, the San Francisco Police Department Literacy Outreach Program, the San Francisco Fire Department Association, the Lower Haight Merchants Association, and the Lower Haight Residents Association. In addition to monetary donations, we also donate art supplies to local children’s groups, food to the local food bank, and medical cannabis to hospices for non- ambulatory and terminally ill patients. We are continually expanding our charitable donation program and are always looking for new local programs to support.

Please take a moment to learn more about the Charities and resource centers that we feel are important to our members, neighbors and over all San Francisco Community.

		African American Cultural Center
		<a href="http://www.aaacc.org">www.aaacc.org</a>

		The Safety Network Program 
		<a href="http://www.safetynetwork.org">www.safetynetwork.org</a>

		Haight Ashbury Medical Center
		<a href="http://www.hafci.org">www.hafci.org</a>

		Harvey Milk Recreational Center
		<a href="http://www.sfgov.org/site/recpark">www.sfgov.org/site/recpark</a> 

		Hayes Valley Community Center
		Laguna Honda Hospital & Rehabilitation 
		<a href="http://www.lagunahonda.org">www.lagunahonda.org</a>

		Maitri Compassionate Care 
		<a href="http://www.maitrisf.org">www.maitrisf.org</a>

		Project Safety
		San Francisco AIDS Foundation
		<a href="http://www.sfaf.org">www.sfaf.org</a>

		San Francisco Aids LIFECYCLE 
		<a href="http://www.aidslifecycle.org">www.aidslifecycle.org</a>

		San Francisco Fire Fighters Charitable Foundation
		<a href="http://www.ffcf.org">www.ffcf.org</a>

		San Francisco Police Officers Association [POA]
		<a href="http://www.sfpoa.org">www.sfpoa.org</a>

		Project Open Hand
		<a href="http://www.openhand.org">www.openhand.org</a>]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx" title="Accomplishments" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room is committed to making positive contributions to the therapeutic cannabis community and has remained at the forefront of the movement by establishing a comprehensive set of rules and guidelines that govern the safe and compassionate operation of our facility.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx" title="" subtitle="The Vapor Room Cooperative…" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[Was the first dispensary to submit our self- regulation guidelines to the City of San Francisco and to submit a proposal for operational standards throughout the San Francisco medical cannabis community. Was an active and positive participant in the drafting of the SF Medical Cannabis Ordinance from beginning to end. Consistently donates to several local, neighborhood based non- profits and children’s groups that provide after school activities, summer camps, educational field trips and arts and crafts supplies. Works diligently with the Lower Haight Merchants Association (LHMA) advocating public safety on our streets and in our community. Has worked with Police Captains from both the Northern and Park Station Districts and have continual communication with local beat officers. Actively participates in neighborhood clean- up days. Worked with the Lower Haight Merchants Association and the Department of Water and Power to create more lighting and place more trash cans into our neighborhood. Monitors and enforces all double parking violators and driveway blocking on our block, regardless of the fact that much of the nuisance is attributed to other businesses. Monitors the safety and cleanliness of our block, with utmost pride, making an extra effort to keep illicit drug dealers (that once plagued this block) off our block and our of our neighborhood! Has consistently been voted Best Cannabis Dispensary by SFWeekly and SF Bay Guardian readers in their annual “Best Of” issues. Consistently donates to several activist and non- profit organizations that promote awareness of therapeutic cannabis on a State and Federal Level.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx" title="Vapor Room Staff" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[Staff members at the Vapor Room Cooperative consist of highly trained therapeutic cannabis specialists at the counter, experienced security personnel at the doors and compassionate, community minded management. Our staff is considered to be very sympathetic to the many health, social and economic issues that affect San Francisco patients of all walks of life as well as friendly and informative. The men and women that make up the Vapor Room Cooperative have always made compassionate dispensing of therapeutic cannabis their top priority. They have also been trained to provide basic assistance to our disabled patients and are First Aid/ CPR certified bi- annually, having just renewed in July 2009.

Having witnessed first hand the relief therapeutic cannabis brings to suffering patients, especially the ever- increasing number of those who do not benefit from prescribed narcotics for pain management and those who do not benefit from prescribed anti- anxiety and depression medications, our staff is committed to educating patients properly so they can choose the medication that best serves their needs.]]></textnode>

	</body>
</about>