<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<legalresources>
	<body header="Legal Rights & Resources">	
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="State Medical Cannabis Laws" subtitle="Proposition 215">
			<blurb><![CDATA[Proposition 215 was a proposition in the state of California on the November 5, 1996 ballot. It passed with 5,382,915 (55.6%) votes in favor and 4,301,960 (44.4%) against. Also known as the Compassionate Use Act of 1996, the proposition was a state-wide voter initiative authored by Dennis Peron, Valerie Corral, Dale Gieringer, William Panzer, Steve Kubby, San Francisco oncologists Richard Cohen and Ivan Silverberg, and by nurse Anna Boyce of Orange County, and approved by California voters. It allows those with a valid doctor's recommendation to possess and cultivate marijuana for personal medical use. The Act added Section 11362.5 to the California Health and Safety Code. This law has caused much conflict in the United States between states' rights advocates and those who support a stronger federal presence. Although "Compassionate Use" is now protected in California law, the federal government continues to effect prosecutions under the Controlled Substances Act. The constitutionality of the act was recently challenged, but subsequently upheld by the Supreme Court (cf. Gonzales v. Raich). Upon announcement of the Supreme Court decision, California Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger briefly suspended the operation of programs related to compassionate use, but was compelled to resume after Attorney General Bill Lockyer issued a memo stating the Supreme Court ruling does not change any laws involving medical marijuana in California, it only confirmed that federal raids by the DEA were in fact legal and could continue to take place.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="California State Senate Bill 420">
			<blurb><![CDATA[Senate Bill 420 was passed by the California Legislature to address vague provisions of Proposition 215. The bill was signed into effect by outgoing Governor Gray Davis in 2003. which reflects a compromise between patients’ advocates and law enforcement, includes controversial state guidelines regarding how much Marijuana patients may grow and possess without being subject to arrest. It also requires counties to implement a voluntary patient identification card system and other provisions to protect patients and their caregivers from arrest. The guidelines, which were hotly disputed by California NORML and other patients’ advocates, allow patients up to 6 mature or 12 immature plants and up to one-half pound of dried, processed marijuana. Patient advocates had pushed for more liberal guidelines, such as those adopted by Sonoma County, which allow up to 99 plants in a 100 square foot growing area plus 3 pounds of marijuana. The final guidelines were decided in a last-minute legislative deal by Attorney General Lockyer and Sen. Vasconcellos in order to get the bill passed. In other provisions, SB 420: • Recognizes the right of patients and caregivers to associate collectively or cooperatively to cultivate medical marijuana . • Disallows marijuana smoking in no smoking zones, within 1000 feet of a school or youth center except in private residences, on school buses, in a motor vehicle that is being operated, or while operating a boat.. • Protects patients and caregivers from arrest for transportation and other miscellaneous charges not covered in 215. • Allows probationers, parolees, and prisoners to apply for permission to use medical marijuana; however, such permission may be refused at the discretion of the authorities. • Makes it a crime to fraudulently provide misinformation to obtain a card, to steal or misuse the card of another, to counterfeit a card, or to breach the confidentiality of patient records in the card program.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Legal Resources" subtitle="Green Aid - Legal Defense Fund">
			<blurb><![CDATA[As a new player in this diverse arena, GREEN AID seeks to establish itself as a key partner among others already hard at work for marijuana reform over the last three decades.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.green-aid.com]]></website>
		</textnode>	

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Medical Cannabis Reports">
			<blurb><![CDATA[CannabisMD reports news and views on the state of medical marijuana in Washington.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.cannabismd.com]]></website>
		</textnode>	

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Medical Marijuana Patients Union">
			<blurb><![CDATA[The Patients Rights Network Formed by and for people who use cannabis medicines for beneficial health purposes.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.mmpu.org]]></website>
		</textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Oakland Cannabis Buyers Co-Op">
			<blurb><![CDATA[The goal of the Oakland Cannabis Buyers’ Cooperative (OCBC) is to provide seriously ill patients with a safe and reliable source of medical cannabis information and patient support.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.rxcbc.org]]></website>
		</textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Wo/Mens Alliance for Medical Marijuana">
			<blurb><![CDATA[The Wo/Men’s Alliance for Medical Marijuana (WAMM) is a collective of seriously ill patients who work to educate the general public regarding the medical benefits of marijuana.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.wamm.org]]></website>
		</textnode>	
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Patient Activism" subtitle="">
			<blurb><![CDATA[It is critical that you, the patients and citizens of this city, let your voices be heard (democracy only works when you participate!). Please call, email, or write your supervisor and let them know that you support continuing to allow medical cannabis dispensaries in ALL districts of San Francisco!]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="San Francisco District Supervisors">
			<blurb><![CDATA[	District  1 Eric Mar
	District  2 Michela Alioto- Pier
	District  3 David Chiu
	District  4 Carmen Chu
	District  5 Ross Mirkarimi
	District  6 Chris Daly
	District  7 Sean Elsbernd
	District  8 Bevan Dufty
	District  9 David Campos
	District 10 Sophie Maxwell
	District 11 John Avalos]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.sfgov.org]]></website>
		</textnode>	
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Americans For Safe Access">
			<blurb><![CDATA[Americans for Safe Access is the largest national grassroots coalition working to protect the rights of patients and doctors to legally use marijuana for medical purposes.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.safeaccessnow.org]]></website>
		</textnode>	
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Marijuana Policy Project">
			<blurb><![CDATA[Marijuana Policy Project (MPP) is the largest marijuana policy reform organization in the United States. MPP focuses on removing criminal penalties for marijuana use, with a particular emphasis on making marijuana medically available to seriously ill people.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.mpp.org]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Drug Policy Alliance">
			<blurb><![CDATA[The Alliance is the nation’s leading organization working to end the war on drugs. Among other causes, the Drug Policy Alliance works to make marijuana legally available for medical purposes.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.drugpolicy.org]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="NORML Organization">
			<blurb><![CDATA[California NORML is a non-profit, membership organization dedicated to reforming California’s marijuana laws. Our mission is to establish the right of adults to use cannabis legally.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.canorml.org]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="SB420 Text">
			<blurb><![CDATA[California Senate Bill 420 (HS 11362.7) Medical Marijuana Implementation.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.chrisconrad.com/expert.witness/sb420-03.htm]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Hemp Evolution">
			<blurb><![CDATA[Cannabis activist information and marijuana resources.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.hempevolution.org]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Medical" subtitle="SF DPH Medical Cannabis ID Card Program">
			<blurb><![CDATA[Medical Cannabis Voluntary Identification Card Program Description and Application Instructions.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.dph.sf.ca.us/services/mcidinfo.htm]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="California State Medical Marijuana Forms">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.cdph.ca.gov/pubsforms/forms/Pages/MedicalMarijuanaProgram.aspx]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="MediCann">
			<blurb><![CDATA[MediCann is an organization of alternative medicine clinics committed to providing a stress-free, holistic environment where patients in need of medicinal marijuana receive a cost-effective, expert evaluation by a licensed medical professional.]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.medicannusa.com]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="NEARBY HEALTH & MEDICAL FACILITIES" subtitle="Castro Holistic Health Center">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[2191 Market St # D San Francisco, CA 94114]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 864 3453]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="The Women's Community Clinic">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[2166 Hayes Street, Suite 104, San Francisco, CA 94117]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 379 7800]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Maitri AIDS Hospice">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[401 Duboce Ave. San Francisco, CA 94117]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 558 3000]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.maitri.org]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Haight Medical Center">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[1342 Haight St San Francisco, CA 94117]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 552 0916]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="California Pacific Medical Center">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[45 Castro Street San Francisco, CA 94114]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[415 600 6000]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Natural Medicine Works">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[207A Sanchez Street, San Francisco, CA 94117]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 513 7270]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.natmedworks.com]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Schizandra Health Center">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[493 Sanchez St, San Francisco, CA 94117]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 553 8886]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="UCSF Medical Center">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[350 Parnassus Ave # 706 San Francisco, CA 94143]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 476 6880]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.ucsfhealth.org]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Grace Medical Center">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[1660 Geary Blvd San Francisco, CA 94115.]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 931 2015]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Saint Mary's Medical Center">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[450 Stanyan St # A San Francisco, CA 94117]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 668 1000]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.stmarysmedicalcenter.org]]></website>
		</textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Haight Ashbury Free Medical Clinic">
			<blurb><![CDATA[]]></blurb>
			<address><![CDATA[612 Clayton St San Francisco, CA 94117]]></address>
			<phonenumber><![CDATA[415 487 5632]]></phonenumber>
			<website><![CDATA[www.hafci.org]]></website>
		</textnode>												
	</body>
</legalresources>