<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- 
  ]]></textnode>

<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[
-->

<member>
	<information header="Information">	
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Introduction" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[Although cannabis is recognized as a legal medicine in California, many people do not understand its therapeutic benefits and often stereotype and discriminate against therapeutic cannabis patients who do not “look sick.” It is important to note that patients with serious conditions might not appear “sick”, especially if they are in the early stages of their illness. We serve a diverse group of patients suffering a myriad of conditions including but not limited to: HIV/AIDS, ADHD, Arthritis, Cancer, Colitis, Crohn’s Disease, Epilepsy, Fibromyalgia, Glaucoma, Hepatitis C, Anxiety, Depression, Surgery Recovery and many more.]]></textnode>
	
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Required Documentation" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[In order to become a Vapor Room Cooperative member you must have a valid Doctor’s recommendation for therapeutic cannabis use, and valid CA identification.  We strongly recommend that you also obtain the State of California medical cannabis verified ID card.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Required Forms & Process" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[Membership is given on an annual basis and is only valid with a current doctor’s recommendation.  Members are informed of their membership rights and responsibilities [see below] and are asked to sign a statement acknowledging that they understand their rights and responsibilities and that their membership can be revoked if they violate any of the rules. All forms are kept off- site, ensuring patient confidentiality.  Members receive a Vapor Room Cooperative member ID number. When a patient visits the cooperative, their ID number is used to verify that s/he is a member of the cooperative in good standing and has a current, valid doctor’s recommendation for medical cannabis use. ]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Voluntary Forms" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[In addition to serving our members’ needs, the Vapor Room Cooperative also strives to increase the understanding of medical cannabis in our greater community and advocates for its legal use in California.  We collect data on a voluntary basis from our patients including demographic and medical information.  This data helps us better understand the nature of the medical use of cannabis in our community and allows us to educate others including city and state decision-makers and medical researchers.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Caregiver Members" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[Caregiver membership is given in conjunction with patient membership.  In order for a caregiver to be eligible for membership, their patient must already be a member of the cooperative.  We recommend the patient and caregiver come in together with all required documentation and register for membership at the same time.  We do make exceptions for caregivers of seriously ill and non-ambulatory patients who are unable to come in to register for membership.  In this case, the caregiver would be required to bring in their patient’s doctor’s recommendation, valid CA identification as well as the their caregiver paperwork.  We will call the patient’s doctor to verify their medical cannabis recommendation.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Membership Rights, Responsibilities &
Codes of Conduct" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room Cooperative is founded on respect and compassion for our patients and our community. We are committed to serving our member patient needs with the highest level of compassion and professionalism. By becoming a member of the Vapor Room Cooperative, you are becoming a part of our growing community of medical marijuana patients and advocates.

Membership responsibilities are important for providing a welcoming atmosphere for your fellow members and our neighbors, and are critical to ensuring the Vapor Room Cooperative stays open and is able to continue serving our patient’s needs.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Becoming a member of the 
Vapor Room Cooperative means
that you have the RIGHT to" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[Be treated with respect and compassion by the staff and fellow cooperative members.
			
A safe, clean environment both inside our doors and outside in our local community.
			
Purchase medical cannabis or visit the counter at up to twice a day.
			
Be assisted by a knowledgeable, caring staff on the type of cannabis that is right for you.
			
Participate in our compassion programs on an as needed basis.
			
Attend the member meeting held annually.
			
Make comments and suggestions to the Board of Directors for how we can improve our cooperative.
			
A handbook that provides detailed information about the operating procedures of the cooperative, medical cannabis, and your legal rights.

Becoming a member of the Vapor Room Cooperative also means that you have the RESPONSIBILITY to:

NEVER resale any medical cannabis.

NEVER double park or block any driveways while parking in the neighborhood.
	
Always be respectful of our neighbors by keeping your voice and stereo down while in the neighborhood.

Always treat your fellow members, the staff, and our neighbors with respect.
	
Always show proof of membership and a valid doctor’s recommendation or verified ID card upon entry.
	
Follow all current and future guidelines set forth by the Vapor Room Cooperative.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Community Codes of Conduct." secondsubtitle="DO…"><![CDATA[Be Aware that YOUR actions in this community affect all of its residents, including Us.
	
Respect our neighbors by keeping your voice and stereo down while in the neighborhood.
	
Have a Polite and Courteous Attitude with our neighbors, staff and patients.
	
Have your driver drop you off in front of the Vapor Room Cooperative & tell your driver to keep the car moving while waiting for you, and to PICK YOU UP in front of the Vapor Room Cooperative.
	
Remember that being a member of the Vapor Room Cooperative is a privilege that You Must Continually Respect.
	
Practice discretion at ALL times while in our community.
	
Keep your medicine in your pocket, AWAY FROM SIGHT
	
Keep Your medicine to yourself, even in your car.
	
Use our facility or the privacy of your own home for taking your medicine, instead of smoking on neighbor stairs, sidewalks or parks.
	
Follow our 90 minute limit for lounging inside the cooperative.
	
Drive Carefully in our community and follow the speed limit.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="DO…"><![CDATA[NOT Block ANY driveways EVER! No Exceptions, No Excuses, Not even for “just one minute, I promise”.
	
NOT Double Park your Car EVER! No Exceptions, No Excuses, NO ENTRY!
	
NOT Distribute, Resale, Break Up or Share your medicine in our community, this includes your friends - even if you are in your car. No Exceptions, No Excuses, NO ENTRY!
	
NOT Use your medicine in public (including sidewalks, stoops, alleys, cars, etc.) Especially in our community!
	
NOT Medicate while driving!

NOT Drive after medicating in our lounge! We will gladly call you a taxi.

NOT Litter! Please throw your trash in a trash can, NOT on our streets (including Vapor Room packaging)!
	
NOT Loiter outside or on neighbor stoops.
	
NOT Have confrontations with our neighbors; Please just Walk Away!
	
NOT Bring children into our facility. Please keep the little ones at home. Thank you!

If a member violates any one of the rules outlined above, their membership will be revoked.  The Vapor Room Cooperative also reserves the right to refuse service to or revoke the membership of any member that acts in such a way to threaten the safety of our Cooperative or violates any current or future rules set forth by the Board of Directors.  The Vapor Room Cooperative of San Francisco is only as strong as our members.  We welcome you to our community and look forward to seeing you at the Vapor Room!]]></textnode>
	
	</information>
	
	<services header="Services">	
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Vaporizer Demonstrations" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[Vaporizing therapeutic cannabis is the safest, most economical method of introducing THC, CBD and Delta- 9 into the body. We offer free vaporizer demonstrations with our top of the line Volcano vaporizers to our members who are not familiar with this great alternative to smoking. We also offer free vaporizer cleanings for our members and discounts on vaporizers for our members on a fixed income.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Therapeutic Cannabis Education" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[One of the founding principles of the Vapor Room Cooperative is to provide education and insight into the complex world of cannabis and all its subtle nuances. There are many different strains and cross- strains available and each one has its own unique properties, characteristics and effects. Our highly trained staff has years of experience providing members with all the information necessary to find the specific relief they need from their symptoms.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Compassion Programs" subtitle="" secondsubtitle=""><![CDATA[The Vapor Room Cooperative has three types of compassion programs whereby we offer medicine free of charge to member- patients in need. The Vapor Room Compassionate Assistance Program This program is available for our fixed income and seriously or terminally ill members. Qualifying members receive high- grade medicine once a week at no cost. On- Site Instant Relief Compassion Program We offer compassionate high grade medicine to our members who are in need of relief on an as needed basis daily. This program was designed to make sure that no member in need of medicine is turned away for lack of funds. We gladly offer a dose of high- grade medicine for the patient to medicate with ONSITE daily. The Vapor Room Compassionate Service Program For terminally ill, hospice and bed- bound members who are not able to visit our facility, we offer weekly home/ hospice visits to deliver high grade cannabis, edibles and other donations. We donate more than enough medicine to ensure these patients will be able to self medicate at their discretion and at their individual need levels.

Additionally, veterans, senior citizens, and patients on a fixed income are always treated generously.  For the majority of our patients who do not qualify for these compassion programs, we regularly give away edibles and rolled cannabis when available, as well as samples of new products.]]></textnode>
		
		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="Community Center" subtitle="Health & Well Being Programs" secondsubtitle="Yoga/Tai Chi Sessions"><![CDATA[Yoga acts both as a curative and preventive therapy for many ailments. Yoga and Tai Chi practices help balance the nervous and endocrine systems, which in turn directly influence all the other systems and organs of the body. The very essence of yoga and tai chi practice lies in attaining mental peace, improved concentration, and a relaxed state of living.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Therapeutic Massage"><![CDATA[We offer free therapeutic back and neck massage to our patients twice a week by a Certified Massage Therapist. This service helps our patients who otherwise couldn’t afford massages, feel relaxed and find relief from pain.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="CPR Certification"><![CDATA[Classes provided by CPR Education & Seminars LLC. All curriculums follow the updated ECC Guild guidelines acknowledged by the collaboration of the American Heart Association with the Liaison committee on Resuscitation.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Fresh Fruit Daily"><![CDATA[Organic, locally grown fresh fruit is delivered every Wednesday and available for Members to snack on while in the lounge. This scrumptious treat is purchased from <a href="http://www.farmfreshtoyou.com">www.farmfreshtoyou.com</a>]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Nutritional Counseling"><![CDATA[Covers a variety of assessments and solutions regarding the quality of nutrition in a diet. Our nutritionist offers personalized education in nutritional facts, eating habits, nutrients, allergies and can also help harmonize side effects of prescription medications.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Art Therapy Classes"><![CDATA[Visual expression is an important tool for personal reflection of emotional and cognitive growth. Art Therapy classes will help our members work through their stress related symptoms and traumatic experiences by developing a safe and creative environment where members can learn personal expression and awareness through the use of a variety of art materials, such as paints, markers, stenciling and photography.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Support Group Sessions" secondsubtitle="Living with HIV & AIDS"><![CDATA[This Group is designed to help fight isolation, depression and other stresses that affect the health of persons living with HIV/AIDS. This group will provide our HIV+/AIDS members an outlet for sharing experiences and information while building a strong social support system.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Cancer Survivors Group"><![CDATA[Understanding that emotional support is just as important as physical care when diagnosed with cancer this group helps our members maintain a positive outlook on life and remain optimistic while experiencing the many phases of cancer, diagnosis, treatment and aftercare.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Grief Counseling Group"><![CDATA[Knowing that bereaved individuals tend to heal more quickly when in a supportive environment, we are providing a group that will have professional counseling for people experiencing grief from bereavement, chronic and/or life- threatening illness. Members in similar situations will be able to share their experiences with others who have been in similar situations.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="xxx"  title="" subtitle="Resources" secondsubtitle="Legal Peer Counseling with 
Americans for Safe Access"><![CDATA[This service helps to answer the many legal, medical and political questions and concerns that being a therapeutic cannabis patient entails. Questions ranging from what to do in an encounter with law enforcement to which politicians support medical cannabis. More information is available at <a href="http://www.safeaccessnow.org">www.safeaccessnow.org</a>]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Vapor Room Member Volunteer Program"><![CDATA[Our Member Volunteer Program is a great way for our staff and members to give back to both the Lower Haight community and to the many charities in San Francisco that need help.  Member Volunteers not only experience the positive feeling of giving but are able to socialize and develop new friendships.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="SF Food Bank Volunteers"><![CDATA[Member Field Trips for our members who seldom are able to participate in what our wonderful City has to offer. Field trips are also a great way for our members to socialize with each other. Field trips planned include Movie Theatres, Museums, Walking Tours, and Community Gardens]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Community Benefits"><![CDATA[The Lower Haight Community will also greatly benefit from the opening of the VRCenter. We will be able to host a variety of meetings, classes and events.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Career Counseling"><![CDATA[Find your inner passion, get professional satisfaction, tips for networking, interviewing, sales skills, negotiations. This is a 6 week program meeting once a week for an hour and a half.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Life Coaching"><![CDATA[Get inspired, create a dream/vision, transform your life and bring success into your life. This is a 6 week program: meeting once a week meeting for an hour and a half.]]></textnode>

		<textnode divider="ooo"  title="" subtitle="" secondsubtitle="Vapor Room Center"><![CDATA[The Lower Haight Community will also greatly benefit from the opening of the VRCenter. We will be able to host a variety of meetings, classes and events such as Merchant Association meetings, Resident Association meetings, NERT training classes, a Community Art Gallery, SPCA / Animal Rescue, Neighborhood Cleanups, and Laguna Honda Hospice patient visits.]]></textnode>

	</services>
	
</member>